<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal CS Portfolio on Yuval Ashkenazi</title>
    <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal CS Portfolio on Yuval Ashkenazi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pinochle: Logic-Based Prolog</title>
      <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>This project is an implementation of the Pinochle card game written with a logic-based design in Prolog. The project was written as the fourth part of Organization of Programming Languages course (CMPS-366) at Ramapo college during the Fall 2020 semester. Additionally, the project features a serialization option of saving the game&amp;rsquo;s state into a file as well as loading a game from a file.
Link to GitHub Repository</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinochle: Event-Driven Java/Android</title>
      <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>This project is an implementation of the Pinochle card game written with an Event-Driven design in Java/Android. The project was written as the third part of Organization of Programming Languages course (CMPS-366) at Ramapo college during the Fall 2020 semester. The project contains 8 different classes. Additionally, the project features a serialization option of saving the game&amp;rsquo;s state into a file as well as loading a game from a file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Quality Machine Learning Classifier</title>
      <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>This research project was part of the Machine Learning class at Ramapo College (CMPS-320).
It presents the classification of air quality levels in India based on data that has been collected prior to and during the Covid-19 pandemic. The data was collected in order to identify the effects of shutting down the world for several months on the quality of air and could later be used to define the necessary precautions that need to be taken in order to decrease humans’ negative effects on the quality of air and our environment as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinochle: Functional Programming in Common LISP</title>
      <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>This project is an implementation of the Pinochle card game written in a functional design in Common LISP. The project was written as the second part of Organization of Programming Languages course (CMPS-366) at Ramapo college during the Fall 2020 semester. Additionally, the project features a serialization option of saving the game&amp;rsquo;s state into a file as well as loading a game from a file.
Writing this project was my first experience with functional programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinochle: Object Oriented in C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>This project is an implementation of the Pinochle card game written in an Object Oriented design and Polymorphic behavior in C++. The project was written as the first part of Organization of Programming Languages course (CMPS-366) at Ramapo college during the Fall 2020 semester.
The project contains 8 different classes. Additionally, the project features a serialization option of saving the game&amp;rsquo;s state into a file as well as loading a game from a file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The VC-3600 Assembler</title>
      <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>This project is a multi-class project written in C++ as the final project for Software Design class in Ramapo College (CMPS361). The Assembler is designed to run the &amp;ldquo;VC-3600&amp;rdquo;- a fictional decimal computer. The program processes the VC-3600 assembly language into machine language. The program also includes an emulator that imitates a specified machine. A sample input file for the program can be found in the github link under &amp;ldquo;prog&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuval-ash1.github.io/Yuval_Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>I invite you to visit my GitHub and LinkedIn pages to view my previous works and connect with me:
   Platform URL     LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuval-ashkenazi/   GitHub: https://github.com/yuval-ash1   Email: yuvyuv@windowslive.com    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
